{
    "id": "dd2df51fc7f94f8394db6376cb9aaaeb",
    "title": "Tenses Gap Filling Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Sugar ………………………… flies.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about facts. Sugar is a singular subject, so write attracts. ",
            "answers": [
                "attract",
                "attracts",
                "is attracting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "24ab7926cb8944518216f3d85a9cee68"
        },
        {
            "question": "Suspense novels ………………………… a special attention for me.",
            "description": "Use the simple present to talk about likes, preferences, tastes etc. ",
            "answers": [
                "are holding",
                "hold",
                "holds"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d52ba40c4ff540578f352297accc8583"
        },
        {
            "question": "The mourners …………………………. in black.",
            "description": "The passive form is required here.",
            "answers": [
                "attired",
                "have attired",
                "were attired"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "1a681e460ebc4ac59257875ad5daf0f6"
        },
        {
            "question": "The defendant ………………………….. by his attorney.",
            "description": "The passive form is required here.",
            "answers": [
                "represented",
                "has represented",
                "was represented"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "31210240a4264bf0b077c97749c9b32b"
        },
        {
            "question": "The accident …………………………. to faulty brakes.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "attributed",
                "was attributed",
                "was contributed"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "1c2ef96d7a9c4425aa0f171d67d393ec"
        },
        {
            "question": "Skydiving …………………………. both audacity and skill.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "takes",
                "taken",
                "is taking"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "f08203a3729845b19cb2d9857c731e76"
        },
        {
            "question": "The audience ………………………… happy with the play.",
            "description": "Either a singular or a plural verb can be used after audience. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "402406d11673469b939c4bcd233aeb77"
        },
        {
            "question": "The settlers ………………………… the burning of the fort by destroying a tribal village.",
            "description": "To avenge is to take vengeance for.",
            "answers": [
                "revenged",
                "avenged",
                "venged"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f0a04f9589284deba3a229a8f003bff3"
        },
        {
            "question": "Cats have an aversion …………………………. wet.",
            "description": "Here to is a preposition. The ing form is used after preposition to. ",
            "answers": [
                "to get",
                "to getting"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "cf91bbdf09f54455ac23df0768cafaeb"
        },
        {
            "question": "People who …………………………. too avid for success may miss some of the joys of life.",
            "description": "When the relative pronoun is the subject, the verb should agree with its antecedent. ",
            "answers": [
                "is",
                "are",
                "have"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "6de1c2c6c57643d1af1f1a14649d6320"
        },
        {
            "question": "The grandparents …………………………… custody of the children.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "have awarded",
                "awarded",
                "were awarded"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "05199ec323a24bc0919e6433b2e12073"
        },
        {
            "question": "The salesman kept babbling, until they ……………………… the door.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "shut",
                "shutted",
                "shutting"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9d8da4b6a3e54fc284fd0bdd55c11d55"
        }
    ]
}